Hilla Muraja - Edinburgh, UK

+447802803871 | hilla.muraja@hotmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/hilla-muraja | https://github.com/HMuraja

Summary

I am a junior software developer, with a Diploma on Full Stack Development and advanced frontend. I have demonstrated my skills in my portfolio projects that can be viewed on my GitHub profile. I have participated 3 hackathons, gaining experience from agile methodologies and teamwork. Additionally, I have been working in Life Science industry for 5 years, providing me experience in problem solving, communication and attention to detail. My experiences in life science led me eventually to the path of software development since developing applications, tools and solutions is what I enjoy the most!

Education

Code Institute2022 – 2023Full Stack Developer Diploma (View Certificate)RemoteUniversity of Turku2015 – 2018Master of Science in Genetics and PhysiologyFinland, TurkuUniversity of Turku2012 – 2015Bachelor of Science in BiologyFinland, Turku

Example Projects

- <u>A Conceptual Website for Boutique Store</u> *Tools Used: HTML, CSS*
- A Randomized Quiz Game Tools Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Instruction Terminal for Cookie Manufacturing Tools Used: HTML, CSS, Python
- Online Recipe Site for Sharing Recipes Tools Used: Django, Python
- Online Book Review Platform Tools Used: Django REST Framework, React, Python, JavaScript

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6, Python

Deployment Platform: Heroku, GitHub

Frameworks: Bootstrap, React, Django, Django REST Framework, JQuery

Design Tools: Figma, Canva, Balsamiq, diagrams.net

Relevant Experience

<u>Code Institute - Career Development</u> (Remote, UK)

Nov 2022 - Present

- Completed a Full Stack Developer course, earning a university credit-rated <u>Certificate</u> equivalent to the Higher National Diploma (HND).
- Completion and submission of 5 projects for review.
- Attendance to Code Institute Hackathons building projects as a team.

Roslin CT - Manufacturing Biotechnologist (Edinburgh, UK)

May 2021 - Nov 2022

- Manufacturing of cell and gene therapy products in a cleanroom environment.
- Use and management of analytical equipment and software.
- Training members of the team in cleanroom activities and equipment use.
- Standardizing form generation with Adobe DC pro and Java Script.

Roslin CT - Technical Document Writer (Edinburgh, UK)

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

- Maintenance of technical documents of GMP procedures.
- Collaboration with the organization's specialist to ensure document accuracy.
- Uploaded and tracked documentation in Q-pulse.

AstraZeneca - Medical Information and Patient Safety Coordinator (Södertälje, Sweden) Apr 2018 – Dec 2019

- Managed customer communication and tracked the data on Salesforce and Track Wise software.
- Administered team's SOPs in SharePoint and transferred them to company's database.